<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ov on Noboru Saito's page</title><link>https://noborus.github.io/tags/ov/</link><description>Recent content in ov on Noboru Saito's page</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja</language><copyright>&amp;copy;Noboru Saito 2019-2020</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 15:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://noborus.github.io/tags/ov/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ov v0.2.0</title><link>https://noborus.github.io/blog/ov_050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 15:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://noborus.github.io/blog/ov_050/</guid><description>ov v0.5.0をリリースしました。 こちらには書いていませんでしたが、以下のリリースをしていました。 v0.2.0 v0.3.0 v0.3.1 v0.4.0 v0.5.0 これまでの変更で内部的な修正を多くおこない v0.5.0では複数のファイルを別々のドキュメントとして開くように変更しました。 これまで ov *.txt は cat *.txtと同じようにファイルを繋</description></item><item><title>ov v0.2.0</title><link>https://noborus.github.io/blog/ov_020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 10:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://noborus.github.io/blog/ov_020/</guid><description>ov v0.2.0をリリースしました。 検索を正規表現対応にしました 検索を正規表現対応にしました。 検索入力を改善しました。カーソルを移動でき、削除、挿入できるようにしました。 バックスペースと重ね打ちに対応しました ^Hによるバックスペースに対応しました。 a^Ha のように文字にバックスペースして</description></item><item><title>ov v0.1.3</title><link>https://noborus.github.io/blog/ov_013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 10:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://noborus.github.io/blog/ov_013/</guid><description>ov v0.1.3をリリースしました。 行番号モードを追加しました -nオプションをつけての起動又はGキー（トグル）により行番号モードになります。 交互の背景色の仕様を少し変更しました 交互の背景色を付けるモードでは、画面の端から端まで色を付けるように変更しました。 これにより空行でも背景色が</description></item><item><title>Oviewer</title><link>https://noborus.github.io/blog/oviewer_en/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 16:50:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://noborus.github.io/blog/oviewer_en/</guid><description>Introduction to OV - Oviewer.
Install You can also download binaries from the ov release, but for now it is still recommended to go get and download the latest version.
go get -u github.com/noborus/ov cd ov make install Features oviewer is a terminal pager like less or more.
Compressed (gzip, bzip2, zstd, lz4, xz) files can be displayed as they are. Better Unicode support. Can also display combined characters that can be displayed in the terminal (if fonts are available). Better wide (full-width) character support. Can be fixed by specifying the number of rows in the header. Ability to switch between wrapping and non-wrapping lines. Background color can be added to every 1 lines. Supports display from psql and mysql. The contents of the current screen can be exported at the end. The goal is to use the PAGER environment variable without problems.</description></item><item><title>ov</title><link>https://noborus.github.io/blog/oviewer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 14:50:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://noborus.github.io/blog/oviewer/</guid><description>私が作成中のovの紹介です。 最初Oviewerというレポジトリ名でしたが、コマンド名に合わせるようにovに変更しました。 インストール ov のリリースからバイナリもダウンロードできますが、今はまだgo getで最新をダウンロードして使うことをオススメします。 ※ 2020/5/11追記。現在</description></item></channel></rss>