<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>go on Noboru Saito's page</title><link>https://noborus.github.io/categories/go/</link><description>Recent content in go on Noboru Saito's page</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja</language><copyright>&amp;copy;Noboru Saito 2019</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 16:50:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://noborus.github.io/categories/go/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Oviewer</title><link>https://noborus.github.io/blog/oviewer_en/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 16:50:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://noborus.github.io/blog/oviewer_en/</guid><description>Introduction to OV - Oviewer.
Install You can also download binaries from the ov release, but for now it is still recommended to go get and download the latest version.
go get -u github.com/noborus/ov cd ov make install Features oviewer is a terminal pager like less or more.
Compressed (gzip, bzip2, zstd, lz4, xz) files can be displayed as they are. Better Unicode support. Can also display combined characters that can be displayed in the terminal (if fonts are available). Better wide (full-width) character support. Can be fixed by specifying the number of rows in the header. Ability to switch between wrapping and non-wrapping lines. Background color can be added to every 1 lines. Supports display from psql and mysql. The contents of the current screen can be exported at the end. The goal is to use the PAGER environment variable without problems.</description></item><item><title>Oviewer</title><link>https://noborus.github.io/blog/oviewer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 14:50:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://noborus.github.io/blog/oviewer/</guid><description>私が作成中のOV - Oviewerの紹介です。 インストール ov のリリースからバイナリもダウンロード出来ますが、今はまだ go getで最新をダウンロードして使うことをお勧めします。 go get -u github.com/noborus/ov cd ov make install 特徴 lessやmoreのようなTerminal pagerです。 圧縮(gzip, bzip2, zstd, lz4, xz)され</description></item><item><title>GoのTUIで表示が崩れる場合</title><link>https://noborus.github.io/blog/runewidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 16:10:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://noborus.github.io/blog/runewidth/</guid><description>結論 gnome-terminalを使用している場合は、設定の「曖昧幅の文字(W)」と環境変数RUNEWIDTH_EASTASIANを一致させよう。 Ambiguous width(曖昧幅) ターミナル上のアプリケーション(TUI)では、GUIと違って文字単位で描画されます。 そして1文字の幅は固定されて</description></item></channel></rss>